Hey! Hey, you!
Well, my feelings are
you're a two-time louse,
just like all the rest of them.
What's going on here?
At the moment, you're interrupting
Mrs. Sutcliffe's session, Mr. Cassidy.
What's the problem?
I took three connecting flights
on three different airlines to get here.
Nobody but you people
are supposed to know I'm here.
- No one does.
- Oh, yeah?
What about the photographer
I caught sneaking around my suite?
I'll notify Security.
Brett Cassidy, the movie star?
Oh, I'm a great admirer of yours.
I rarely go to movies,
but I've seen most of your pictures.
Barbara Sutcliffe.
All right, Mr. Cassidy, if you'll go
to your suite, I'll contact Security,
and I'm sure
they'll check everything out, okay?
Listen to me, you guaranteed me
my confidentiality and my privacy.
We'll talk about that
during your session.
Would you like me to escort you
back to your suite?
- No, I think I can find it, thank you.
- It was nice meeting you.
- Can I help you, Mr. Patterson?
- I'm next.
Isn't that that movie actor,
what's-his-name?
- That's him.
- That's what I thought.
- He's not as tall as you'd expect.
- They never are.
Excuse me?
- Hello?
- Mr. Matlock.
Mr. Matlock.
The janitor let me in.
I must've fallen asleep. I was awake
all night on the bus, then I came here.
Excuse me.
- Do I know you?
- Cassie. Cassie Phillips from Chicago.
Chicago?
You gave a lecture there
at the university last March.
I remember that.
What can I do for you?
Well, I'm here about the job.
What job?
The one you promised me in Chicago,
as your assistant.
- Assistant?
- Right after the lecture,
I interviewed you
for the school paper.
My shoes.
I took them off when I began to nap
while I was waiting for you to come in.
Don't take that as a criticism,
because it's not.
I mean, a lot of people in your position
start work late.
Miss Phillips,
I think we have
a serious misunderstanding here.
- We do?
- I don't know who you are.
Well, I sent you a registered letter.
Where's my purse? Excuse me.
I know I kept the receipt.
I don't remember
offering you any employment.
Well, I looked different then.
I had pink hair, remember?
Oh, with all those little things
in your ear?
Yeah. Well,
when I decided to become a lawyer,
well, I obviously needed a new look.
- You graduated?
- Yes.
- From the university?
I just enrolled at Baxter Law School.
And that's why I'm so grateful to you,
because Baxter requires
all its first-year students to be interns.
And so when I told--
Oh, so Baxter let you in
because they think
you're working for me?
Yes.
How did that happen?
I wrote it on my application.
Miss Phillips, you actually told them
you had a job here?
- Well, I'm sorry--
- You mean you won't give me a job?
- There's no job to give.
- But what about that empty office?
It's not empty.
That's my daughter Charlene's office.
She's in Philadelphia right now
working on a case.
Miss Phillips,
there is no job.
I don't know
how I can say it any plainer.
I'm sorry.
Well, I guess
it was just a misunderstanding, huh?
I guess so.
Well, I guess
I don't have to go to law school.
I mean, a girl my age
has lots of options.
Lots of them.
Listen, thanks anyway.
I'm sure this was all my fault.
I must have assumed too much.
You know how impulsive
young people can be. They--
They get inspired
by someone like yourself.
They wanna model themselves
after them.
Get carried away.
Nice seeing you again. Bye.
Wait a minute.
I suppose
there are some odds and ends
that could be done around here.
Filing things and taking things
to the courthouse and...
Only temporary,
till you find yourself a new position.
Oh, thank you.
I really appreciate this.
Put your things in Charlene's office
for now.
Oh, they're already in there.
I'll get started right away.
Are you free for lunch?
No.
No problem.
I'll be in here, if you need me.
And if you change your mind
about lunch.
--final, 1 1 1- 1 1 0.
And that's it for sports.
Bonnie McGrath's up next
with entertainment. Bonnie?
And do we have news tonight.
Women of Atlanta, hold on tight,
because guess who's come to town.
Anonymous sources tell us
that heartthrob star of stage
and screen Brett Cassidy
is making a pit stop
at the Halvern Clinic,
nationally known sex clinic
here in Atlanta.
What's his problem?
Well, we don't know yet.
But the way we hear it,
the quarterback of romance
may be having trouble
scoring that winning touchdown.
More on this story
as the juicy details become available.
In other entertainment--
Okay, Halvern,
this has gone far enough...
I don't know.
I guess the person that took my picture
could've been working
for the TV station.
But I don't understand
how they knew I was at the clinic.
Dr. Halvern assured me
that all the patients were registered
under fictitious names.
I don't get it. I don't get it.
I don't understand any of it.
That's a real puzzle, isn't it?
- Who are you?
- I'm Mr. Matlock's assistant.
So you didn't notice
that your isometric bar was missing?
No, I didn't.
I don't carry it with me all the time.
- Are you an attorney?
- Not exactly.
So someone could've taken it
during your session
- when you didn't have it with you?
- That's possible.
If you're not an attorney, why are you
asking me all these questions?
I told you,
I'm Mr. Matlock's assistant.
Am I interrupting something?
Oh, hi.
This is Ben Matlock.
This is Brett Cassidy.
You know, from Hollywood.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
Mr. Cassidy was here early,
so I thought we'd get some
of the preliminaries out of the way.
Would you just excuse us
for a moment?
It was a pleasure meeting you,
Mr. Cassidy.
What do you think you're doing?
Getting a statement about what
happened the night of the murder.
Shall I give it to you from the top?
- I know all about it.
- You do?
Sam Young told me this morning
down at the jail.
- Who's Sam Young?
- His local counsel.
Cassie,
I'm not the new kid on the block.
You are.
Yeah. Well, I guess
I could type these notes out for the file.
Yeah, do that. Type them up, file them,
file this stuff, file everything.
And after you've filed everything,
go through the classifieds.
I'll handle the case.
You're not my assistant.
You're just here temporarily
till you find another job, remember?
The classifieds.
Couldn't I do it
after Mr. Cassidy leaves?
I could sort of stand silently by
and take notes while you ques--
- Cassie.
- The classifieds.
He has no idea
who stole his isometric bar.
Classifieds.
So...
Sam Young arrange your bail?
That's right. Said you were
the best defence attorney in town.
Did he say I don't work for free?
Money's no problem.
Well, you don't look like you've missed
too many Thanksgivings.
What happened out there?
Well, I had my session
with Dr. Halvern in the morning,
went back to see him last night,
he was dead.
District attorney
says he has witnesses
that you had an argument
with Dr. Halvern.
Dr. Halvern assured me that
no one would know I was at the clinic.
Then this local TV vulture
uses me as the cover story
for the evening news.
Well, where were you
at the time of the murder?
- In my suite.
- Alone?
That's right.
You're not allowed to bring anybody
with you when you stay at the clinic.
Why not?
You're just not.
Yeah, but why not?
Well, you see, the idea
is to cleanse the mind and the body,
remove yourself from the day-to-day
life pressures while you're there,
so when you go back,
you can function better.
Function better?
That's right, function better.
I have one other question.
Did you do it?
- Do what?
- Kill Dr. Halvern.
No, sir, I didn't.
- Okay, you got a lawyer.
- Thank you.
Now, just curious,
this ''functioning better'' part,
what exactly goes on
in those sessions?
I don't wanna talk about it.
I didn't mean to press.
This is where
the guard found Dr. Halvern.
There doesn't appear
to have been much of a struggle.
Were you the last person
to see Dr. Halvern alive?
No, he had a patient at 7:00.
- Who was that?
- Mrs. Barbara Sutcliffe.
This Mrs. Sutcliffe was here
till 8:00?
She would've left
ten minutes before that.
The standard therapy hour
is 50 minutes.
The 50-minute hour.
It allows the doctor time to make notes
and organise his thoughts
between patients.
Right.
You wanted to see me?
Mr. Matlock, this is Alex Fenton.
He was on duty that night.
- Mr. Fenton, you a doctor?
- Oh, no, no. I'm a technician.
I take care of the equipment.
- What equipment?
- The video and other equipment.
Dr. Halvern
recorded all his sessions.
Well, didn't that
make his patients uncomfortable?
They didn't know.
Thank you, Alex.
What happens to the clinic
now that Dr. Halvern's dead?
It hasn't been decided yet.
You were engaged to him at one time,
weren't you?
That was a long time ago.
It's a shame you didn't marry.
This would've been yours.
One last question.
I was in my office
writing reports alone.
Well, thank you.
Thank God you're here.
Now, there are these two
and there's a suitcase in the bedroom.
If you want a tip,
you'd better get moving.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Sutcliffe,
but I'm afraid
we're not going anywhere.
- Well, what's this?
- That is a subpoena.
And you can keep the change.
But you can't do this.
I've got a plane to catch.
I'm sorry, but we're gonna need you
to testify at the trial.
Why do you need me?
Aren't they going to
convict Brett Cassidy?
We're defending him.
- These belong to you?
- No. No.
No? I didn't think so.
Didn't look like the kind of key ring
that you would have.
See you at the trial.
- Yeah?
- Hi. You Josh Patterson?
- Who wants to know?
- Special delivery.
- What's this?
- It's a subpoena.
What'd you come up with?
Barbara Sutcliffe,
she's a regular at the clinic.
She's been married five times.
She checks in there
after every divorce.
You think she just gets tired of them,
or there's something wrong?
You know,
there's nothing happening.
Or maybe
she just likes to move around?
Could be.
What about Josh Patterson?
Yeah, what about Josh Patterson?
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
Well, what do they do
in those sessions?
I'm not sure.
Talk about whether they're tense
or nervous or unsure, I guess.
You ever been
to one of these places?
No. Have you?
Not until now.
Well, what about Josh Patterson?
You told me the patients at the clinic
were supposed to stay there alone.
- Yeah.
- Well, he wasn't.
I saw someone else in his suite,
and I swear it looked like a woman.
Do you think
that's part of the therapy?
Might not hurt.
Why don't you see
if you can find out who it is?
- I'm on my way.
- Yeah.
Yeah?
- Evening, Joshua.
- Did Jennifer tell you I was here?
Or did that creep Halvern
call you too?
My daughter suspects you're sleeping
with some broad, and she's right.
I'm here
to try and save my marriage.
What was that?
Clean up your act, boy,
or I'll clean it up for you.
Now, get out of here.
Oh, hi.
What are you doing?
Well, I thought
I'd rearrange these law books
and put them in chronological order.
I hoped I'd be done before you got in,
because I wanted to surprise you.
Cassie,
I'm not looking for any surprises.
I had these books arranged
according to my own system.
Civil law over there,
criminal law over here.
Well, I'm not sure that I can
put them back the way they were,
because I didn't pay too much attention
to the way they were.
I'm very particular
about the way I like things,
and I very much liked things
the way they were.
And I like the music the way it was.
Did you file those petitions
at the courthouse?
No, not yet,
but have I got news for you.
Cassie, those papers
have to be in by today.
I'll do it.
Do you remember Bonnie McGrath,
the TV announcer who did the piece
on Brett Cassidy at the clinic?
Well, the person who tipped her
was a woman.
How do you know?
Because I went to the TV station
and I asked her.
We have a problem.
I figure that the person
who tipped Bonnie
is probably the same person
who set Brett up for the murder.
That's not the problem.
Oh, I know I should've
filed your motions before I went.
That's not the problem.
You're a law student.
You're not supposed to be working
on these cases.
Well, I was just trying to help.
Cassie, you can't go around
asking people questions
when you have no idea
how they'll react.
This is not a game.
Ben, once again,
I am the bearer of good news.
Excuse me,
am I interrupting something?
Tyler, this is Cassie Phillips.
She's a filer. She files things.
She's a temporary filer.
This is Tyler Hudson.
He's an investigator.
He's the one who goes around
and asks people questions, okay?
- Okay.
- What's the good news?
All right, I paid a visit to Mr. Patterson,
and there is a woman in his suite,
but it's not his wife.
Josh Patterson
is married to Jennifer Gellar,
the daughter of Big John Gellar,
as you may remember,
the centimillionaire out of Houston.
Now, take a look at this.
That's Mrs. Patterson.
The woman out at the clinic
is 20 pounds lighter
and 1 0 years younger.
I'll go on and file some things.
Better get a subpoena
on Mr. Patterson's lady friend
right away.
Okay.
It was a woman
who tipped the TV station
that Brett was at the clinic.
Now, how do we know that?
- Cassie.
- Who is she?
I don't know. She showed up here
the other day looking for work,
and I was trying to help her out,
but every time I turn my back,
she's into everything.
Maybe if I keep her with me,
she'll stay out of trouble.
Lay a subpoena on that dame
out there.
You got it.
Get your coat. We're--
- Who are you?
- I wanna talk to you.
No. You get out of here right now
or I'm gonna call Security.
You can't do that.
You're not supposed to be here.
- What do you want?
- I work for Ben Matlock.
He's Brett Cassidy's attorney.
And I'd like to ask you a few questions.
I'm not gonna answer any questions.
I think it would be better all around
if you did.
Do you have a subpoena?
Actually,
I don't happen to have one on me.
Why don't we just assume
that I have one?
Can't we just talk this over informally,
woman-to-woman?
- You know, like that?
- Why?
- Because my life is a mess.
- What?
My life is a mess.
See, I work for Ben Matlock,
but it's only temporary, very temporary,
unless I can show him
that I can really make a contribution.
And if I don't,
well, I'm out of his office,
I'm out of law school,
and I'm generally out of luck.
So I was hoping
that maybe you could just answer
one or two very small questions.
Like what?
Like, why are you here
with a married man?
At first,
I didn't know he was married.
I mean, he didn't mention it
and I didn't ask.
Look, I know I shouldn't be here.
I should get out of here right now,
but he wants me here,
and he's so hard to refuse.
- Does that answer your question?
- I had two.
Okay.
Where were you
when Dr. Halvern was murdered?
Right here with Josh.
All night? I mean,
you're sure he was here all night?
Let's just put it this way:
Neither one of us
really needs any therapy.
Then why come here?
It's quiet. Place to hide out.
Oh, no.
Those guys,
they work for Josh's father-in-law.
Well, get in the bedroom.
I'll take care of it.
- Kimberly Bradshaw?
- She's not in at the moment.
Fellas, please. Where are we going?
Hey.
Hey, wait a minute!
Mrs. Sutcliffe,
you've been a patient
at the Halvern Clinic
for the past two weeks.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, it is.
And you were a patient there
five times before. Is that correct?
Yes. Dr. Halvern
helped me through my divorces.
- How?
- Just talking.
I see.
- Do you own a home at Hilton Head?
- I do.
Did Dr. Halvern stay with you
at your home in Hilton Head
this past July,
the 1 5th through the 22nd?
Yes.
And do you own a cabin
in the Berkshires,
where you and Dr. Halvern
spent two weeks last December?
Yes.
Mrs. Sutcliffe, isn't it true that you
and Dr. Halvern were having an affair?
It's-- It's not exactly a secret,
Miss Sutcliffe.
Yes, we were having an affair.
And isn't it true
that you recently found out
that Dr. Halvern was stepping out
on you, seeing other women
at the same time
he was involved with you?
Yes.
So this man whom you trusted
and to whom you told
your deepest secrets
was deceiving you, wasn't he?
- Yes.
- It made you very angry, didn't it?
Yes.
I call your attention to this set of keys
marked ''Halvern,''
and each key is numbered
consecutively 1 through 20
with this charm.
- Do you recognise them?
- I don't know.
My investigator found them
in your bungalow.
So?
Well, these keys open all the doors
at the clinic.
What were they doing
in your bungalow?
Well, I suppose the technician,
Mr. Fenton,
must've left them there
when he came by to repair my TV.
The cable on my TV.
What's so special about them?
Well, with these keys,
you could've unlocked the door
to Brett Cassidy's suite,
stolen his isometric bar,
and since you were Dr. Halvern's
last patient the night of the murder,
you could've entered the therapy room
without knocking.
- Objection.
- Sustained.
Where were you
at the time of the murder?
- In my cottage.
- Alone?
No, Mr. Fenton came by
to fix the cable on my TV.
Mrs. Sutcliffe,
it can't have taken Mr. Fenton
more than ten minutes
to fix the cable on your TV.
It didn't.
Well, what time
did Mr. Fenton leave?
Nine a.m.
Nine a.m.?
Alex and I have known each other
for almost ten years,
but I'd never realised what a kind
and tender man he really is.
When Carl was murdered,
I was with Alex, Mr. Matlock.
- Is he going to be your next husband?
- Well, as a matter of fact, yes.
Congratulations.
No further questions.
In view of the hour, court is in recess
until 1 0 a.m. tomorrow.
- Thought I had her there for a second.
- Oh, you were doing good for a while.
- Well, there's always tomorrow.
- Yeah, I'm glad about that.
- Ben, Cassie's been kidnapped.
- What are you talking about?
Two guys forced her into a limo
out at the clinic and drove away.
- What was she doing at the clinic?
- I didn't have time to ask.
Go down to Headquarters and get
Lieutenant Daniels on this right away.
I'll go to the office
to see if anybody left a message.
You got it.
Dad?
I just called to see how you were.
Everything's great here.
Lieutenant Daniels, please.
This is an emergency.
Hello?
Who's there?
- Are you all right?
- Perfect.
I've got the police looking for you.
I thought you were kidnapped.
Where have you been?
It's all in my report.
Oh, I filed your motions
at the courthouse.
Then I went out to the clinic
and I saw Kimberly Bradshaw,
the girl staying
in Josh Patterson's bungalow.
Well, Big John's bodyguards
thought I was Kimberly,
so they kidnapped me
instead of Kimberly.
I told Big John that Kimberly
didn't know that Josh was married
and she knows this will never work.
He turned out to be a very nice man.
He's giving Kimberly
a plane ticket home to Burbank.
Yeah, that's where she lives,
Burbank.
He's giving her a monthly allowance
to help her get back on her feet.
Oh, and I forgot
to type in the most important part:
Kimberly and Josh Patterson have
an alibi for the time of the murder.
They were together.
They don't need therapy.
So we can eliminate them
as suspects.
So can people start calling me
your assistant?
You know, a regular job?
I told you the first day,
there is no job.
I was just trying to help you out.
I said maybe you could do a few things
around here:
file something,
deliver some things to the courthouse,
just till you find another position.
But you haven't done just that.
You've flown in all directions.
You've gotten yourself in situations
that could've put you
in all kinds of trouble.
I can't be a part of that.
Now, once again,
there is no job.
I'm sorry,
but that's the end of it.
Hello, Dr. Lindstrom.
Oh, hello, Mr. Matlock.
Were you looking for me?
No, I was just wandering around
trying to get a fresh thought
on this case. I'm kind of stuck.
Sometimes it helps, when you're stuck,
if you just kind of walk around.
- Clears the head.
- I know. I do it all the time.
Yeah. Miss Sutcliffe has Alex
for an alibi. I don't know if I buy that.
And then Kimberly
is Josh Patterson's alibi.
I don't know if I buy that.
Boy, there's a lot of people
speaking up for one another.
Well, I guess
it speaks for their commitment.
Yeah.
You're convinced Brett isn't guilty?
I don't think he is. I really don't.
Dr. Halvern used 60-minute tapes
to record those sessions.
They don't make
50-minute cassettes.
Yeah. Yeah. So he'd just let the tape
run out at the end of each session?
That's correct.
If his last appointment was 7:00,
it's possible the tape was running
when the killer
entered the therapy room.
But then that would mean that
he would have to have been murdered
before 8:00.
Well, anyway...
- Wish I could've been more helpful.
- Oh, you were. You were.
Dr. Lindstrom,
I'm gonna need an expert witness
at court on this stuff.
And since you're the only one I know,
I'm afraid you get the short straw.
- Would you mind?
- Sure. When?
- It's tomorrow.
- What time?
- Nine.
- Oh, that's fine.
Okay.
The police sealed the therapy room,
didn't they, with the tapes inside?
Yes, they did.
Mrs. Sutcliffe told me yesterday
that her session
started 1 5 minutes late.
I think that's what she said.
I wonder if her tape could've run
till 8:1 5.
Well, thanks. Thanks.
And 9:00 sharp.
Old Judge Cooksey's
bad about people coming late.
- I'll be there.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Dr. Lindstrom, you worked closely
with Dr. Halvern, didn't you?
Yes. We worked together
for almost ten years.
So you know
a lot about his practises?
Yes.
Let's...
Let's pretend that I'm a patient
at your clinic.
Now, what happens first?
We take a case history,
try to determine the problem,
determine a therapy programme,
and then you'd start sessions
with Dr. Halvern.
Dr. Halvern
recorded these sessions?
Yes, he did.
- Why?
- So we'd have absolute records.
You knew Dr. Halvern personally
as well as professionally, didn't you?
Yes.
As I understand it, at one time,
you and Dr. Halvern
were engaged to be married.
Yes.
But we decided
we didn't need artificial sanctions
to justify our physical relationship.
That's a pretty modern attitude.
Most people's perceptions about sex
are archaic.
Did you know that Dr. Halvern
was having an affair
with Mrs. Sutcliffe
and several others of the patients?
I find that hard to believe.
Well, I'll tell you what I believe.
I believe that when you found out
about his affairs
with Mrs. Sutcliffe and the others
and you asked him to stop
and he wouldn't, you killed him.
That's absurd.
Your Honour,
this is a preliminary hearing.
Mr. Matlock's speculations
have no place here.
Your Honour,
this is a reasonable line of questioning
that may very well save the court
time, expense
and embarrassment
of trying an innocent man.
I'm going to sustain the objection,
Mr. Matlock.
Yes, sir.
Do you know
who Bonnie McGrath is?
- She's a television reporter, isn't she?
- Oh, yes.
- Did you ever speak with her?
- No.
Isn't it true that you're the one
who called Bonnie McGrath
to tell her that Brett Cassidy
was staying at the clinic?
No.
Isn't it true that you told her
Brett Cassidy was staying at the clinic,
in order to give him
an apparent motive for murder?
- No.
- Objection.
- Asked and answered.
- Sustained.
Dr. Lindstrom, do you remember
our conversation yesterday
about Mrs. Sutcliffe's last appointment
with Dr. Halvern?
Yes. You said you thought
the last few minutes of her tape
might contain footage of the murder.
And Dr. Halvern
labelled all his cassettes, didn't he?
Yes, with the patient's name
and date.
So the cassette
that the court would be interested in
would be labelled,
''Barbara Sutcliffe, February 2, 1 987''?
That's right.
Your Honour, at this time,
in pursuant to the stipulation
we reached in chambers,
I would like to play
and enter into evidence
this video recording.
Proceed.
Now, Dr. Lindstrom,
I have to warn you,
you have no idea what's on this tape.
See, I wasn't quite truthful with you
yesterday when we talked.
I told you that Barbara Sutcliffe's
last therapy session
started 1 5 minutes late, which meant
that her tape would've run till 8:1 5,
which means
if the killer entered the therapy room
after the hour, 8:00,
to kill Dr. Halvern,
that person would've been recorded
on videotape in the act.
Which is why you had to get the tape,
because of that possibility.
So, what we're going to see
is a tape recorded
in Dr. Halvern's therapy room
last night after we talked.
It's a fake.
The cameras weren't on last night.
How do you know?
Because you didn't see
the red record light on the camera?
What you don't know
is I had Mr. Fenton disconnect it.
Now, let's see what you did
in the therapy room.
We've blown up this part of the tape
optically.
Dr. Lindstrom, would you read
the label on that cassette?
Maybe you can't make it out
from there.
It says, ''Barbara Sutcliffe,
February 2, 1 987.''
The day Dr. Halvern was murdered.
Only the killer
would've broken into the therapy room
and would've taken that tape.
Only the killer
would've been afraid
of what was on it.
No further questions.
Your Honour, the defence moves
for a complete dismissal
of all charges against Brett Cassidy.
I'm inclined to grant the motion.
Does the prosecution object?
No objection, Your Honour.
Case dismissed.
This court is adjourned.
Congratulations, Brett.
There they are.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Ben, I was a little worried
about Cassie,
so I stopped by her school.
She's gone.
Her roommate said she left for
the bus station about two hours ago.
Where did her roommate
say she was going?
She has no idea.
Mama was right again.
Ain't nothing easy.
Oh, here. Here.
Gentlemen,
what do you say we go to my hotel
and have dinner and celebrate, huh?
You and Tyler go ahead.
I'll catch up to you later.
Shuttle service
to Atlanta International Airport
now boarding at Gate 4.
Mind if I sit down?
Okay.
This bus-station coffee shop's
got the best cinnamon rolls in town.
We won the case.
Congratulations.
So you're going on a trip.
Yep.
Dropped out of law school.
That's a real shame.
You could've made a fine lawyer
someday.
I can be hard sometimes.
Yeah.
And stubborn.
Transway bus to Chicago.
All passengers
should now be boarding.
Transway bus to Chicago.
All passengers
should now be boarding.
You know,
I've had my law office
for a long time,
and I plan to keep it
for a good long time still.
I like it small,
just two or three people.
If there was a young, intelligent,
energetic girl
who, by the way,
did a lot toward winning this case,
if she were to come back
to the office--
She'd still have to mind
once in a while.
And I probably could teach her
a few things.
--you think she'd be interested?
She might.
It'd still be on a trial basis,
and this time
there'd have to be some real rules.
- Rules?
- Well,
I am the senior partner in this outfit,
and before she were to go running off,
talking to people,
asking questions,
getting herself kidnapped,
and things like that,
I think we should talk it over.
Okay?
Okay.
Is that all?
For now.
You free for lunch?
www.tvsubtitles.net